

ANKIT DUSEJA

Full Stack Developer/Product Manager http://ankitduseja.com

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Developer (specialises in Javascript/Frontend). I build web/android/desktop and scalable server applications. I have also worked as a professional blogger earlier.

Preferred tech stack: Javascript, Node.js, React, Express, Mongo/Mysql, Redis, Elasticsearch, Android. I use OS X on my primary machine and linux on my AWS servers.

I have also worked in developing and optimizing products and also interested in Product Management roles.

CONTACT ME

- Bangalore / Bhopal / New Delhi India. IST (UTC + 5:30)
- contact@ankitduseja.com (91) 9893748855
- ankitduseja.com twitter.com/AnkitDuseja linkedin.com/in/ankitduseja angel.co/ankitduseja facebook.com/AnkitDuseja





AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

- ★ Aspire Award for being top performing employee at Times Internet 2015
- ★ Appointed as Board Member in Computer Society of India, VITU. 2013-14
- ✔ Published a paper on "Location Aware News Engine" at SET Conference, VITU. 2013
- ✓ Published a paper on "Secured Wi-Fi Auto-Login for Mobile Devices", VITU. 2012
- ✓ Conducted a symposium on Blogging for students at VIT University 2012
- ★ Appointed as President, Cyber Club, BSSS College, Bhopal 2010-11
- ★ Quoted in Dainik Bhaskar Newspaper as Young Blogging Entrepreneur 2010



WORK EXPERIENCE

SENIOR TECHNICAL OFFICER/DEVELOPER

📑 Times Internet, Noida 📋 Jan 2014-July 2015 🛊 Aspire Award 2015

Architected and developed tech stack for real-time event reporting for times group. Handled and managed front end for multiple campaigns at TOI. Developed several frontend plugins which are also deployed on sites like Gaana.com, Gizmodo, Lifehacker, Business Insider, Huffington Post, etc. Tech Stack: Javascript, HTML5, Redis, ElasticSearch, MySQL, Neo4J, JIRA, etc.

FOUNDER/SELF DEVELOPED PRODUCTS

Various Self Owned Products 💆 2006-Current

Campaigni - Web App - Node.js/MySQL/React/Webpack/Babel/Express Create social image campaigns in seconds.

Facebook Voice - Chrome Extension

Control Facebook with your voice.

Videoshot - Chrome Extension

Capture pixel perfect HTML5 video screenshots.

Boxplore - LAMP Stack - PHP/MySQL/Several other API's

Cross-platform search, boxing and exploring of social content.

Quizzer - Web App - LAMP Stack

A scalable quiz app which was used in VITU.

VOLSBB AutoLogin - Android App - JAVA

A wifi auto-connect app for VITians.

FREELANCER

Various Firms 📋 2010-Current

I freelance on regular basis whenever I have time. I have worked with some international companies in healthtech, brewries and many other industries and helped them with process design, growth, optimization, etc.

Tech Stack: Net, Google Script, Android, jQuery, PHP, Node, Oracle, Chrome, etc



EDUCATION

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

im VIT University, Vellore 📋 July 2011-March 2014 🛊 Board Member, CSI

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATIONS

📠 BSSS College, Bhopal 📋 July 2008-July 2011 👚 President, Cyber Club